

Oleksandr Likvytskyi

Front-end Developer

CONTACT

+48 733 819 952



alex eastwoody@yahoo.com



https://eastwoodyl1c.github.io/web /



linkedin profile

ABOUT ME

I have big experience in my life, graduated as an engineer in renewable sources of energy, then I moved to Poland and living here at this moment working in factories. Now i decide, i have to change my life and as i wanted before, went into the IT specialty. I finished courses as a front-end HTML/CSS+JS developer and continue to improve my skills in this way.

LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate Polish - Intermediate Russian - Native Ukrainian - Native

EDUCATION

Kherson National Technical University

Renewable energy sources. Electrical engineering and electrotechnologies

2010/2015

Lemon School

Front-end (HTML/CSS + JS) Developer 2022/2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

JSC "Khersonoblenergo" | 2017-2018 Engineer

Voss Automotive Poland Sp. o.o. | 2019 - 2020 Production operator

Lear Corporation | 2020 - 2022 Production operator

C+P Sp.z o.o. | 2022 -Welder operator